

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Graduated as a Full stack Web Developer (MERN stack) after a 1 year intensive course, bringing knowledge from Civil Engineering.

Currently Working as a Junior FullStack Developer, learning new technologies and applying my learnings on the go.

SKILLS

Technologies:

- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- jQueryGit
- Github
- Gittiub
- MongoDB

Soft Skills:

- Team Work
- Creativity

React

• Redux

• Redux

AWS

React Native

Material UI

Bootstrap

• Bootstrap

ExpressJS

- Critical Thinking
 Teaching/
 - Teaching/ Mentoring

LANGUAGES

Greek Fluent English C1 Albanian B2 German B1

CONTACT



+49 1577 1514616



b.brisilda1552@hotmail.com



https://brisilda-bushi.com/



Marienfelder Allee 54, 12277, Berlin

SOCIAL







BRISILDA BUSHI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH | Berlin | 11.2020 - 12.2021

- Attending the one year full time course which includes technologies from MERN stack
- Finished and still working on all small and large projects assigned to me/my team successfully

CERTIFIED TRAINING PROFESSIONAL (1 WEEK)

Peter Knapp GmbH Coaches & Catalysts | Berlin | 09.2019 - 09.2019

CERTIFIED TRAINING PROFESSIONAL (1 WEEK)

Arvato Bertelsmann CRM Solution Germany | Berlin | 10.2018 - 10.2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN CIVIL ENGINEERING (BSCE)

Technological Institute of Crete | Iraklion | 10.2010 - 02.2016

 Learned physics, statics and math to be able to calculate the weight power a house needs/uses to make it stable and functional

WORK EXPERIENCE

APP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SKF Lubrication Managment Germany | Berlin | 01.2022 - Present

- Collaborate and bring the company branding, components and design to projects (UI & UX)
- Contribute in Frontend Development using React, Typescript, AWS

DCI WEB DEVELOPER TUTOR

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmbH | Berlin | 01.2021 - 10.2021

- Live Coding and explaining exercises to my fellow students upon requests
- Explaining terms and usage regarding challenging concepts

CUSTOMER SERVICE TRAINER

Bank N26 GmbH | Berlin | 07.2019 - 06.2020

- Schedule training sessions, adjust training curriculum and deliver trainings to new and current employees
- Updating Outsourcing partners, delivering trainings to the trainers and provide advice to them on how to deliver the training from their side
- Meetings which are monthly/weekly regarding up to date information

CUSTOMER SERVICE TRAINER

Arvato Bertelsmann / Majorel | Berlin | 05.2018 - 06.2019